[music]
>> Oil change, two new tires,
new brake pads, new master switch for
the power windows, and fixed coolant
leak.
>> It's a pretty good way to get around.
>> You want to try it?
>> No, it breaks my foot.
>> You sure?
I just need to move this.
>> Yeah.
>> Now just give it a little bit of speed,
just a tiny bit. Just a little bit of
speed.
There it is.
>> [laughter]
>> There's my car.
>> Hi.
>> Okay, how are you? I'm good.
>> That was expensive.
Piggy?
Piggy, you want to go for a drive?
So, the wife and kids already left.
They took a plane this morning. I have
to take all these bags and the dog and
drive there to go meet the family for
vacation. But, I get to take the dog. Go
get it.
>> [music]
>> Ready?
>> Forgot one thing. Stay there.
All right, that's it. We're officially
on the go.
Goodbye, New York City, for now.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Gas.
So, we go every summer, get the kids out
of the city, they go to camp, and it's
very exciting.
That's what this trip is. Candace and
the girls fly, I I drive.
I love it, but that's
that's what the that's what this current
adventure is. That's what this is about.
>> [music]
[music]
>> What else?
We went to stop at Chuck.
>> Did you get groceries?
>> I got like minimum groceries. They They
certainly got a lot of ice cream.
>> [music]
>> Stay here for 1 minute. Stay right here.
I'll be right back.
Quick pit stop in Mystic, Connecticut to
see my best friend from like high
school, my best friend in the whole wide
world. He works here, I think.
>> What are the odds of this?
>> I was coming to surprise you, Joe.
>> guy.
>> [laughter]
>> You sure you don't want to bring her in?
>> No, I'll leave her in the car. She
definitely wants to go in.
She'll cause trouble in there.
>> a haircut?
>> [music]
[music]
>> All right.
>> Okay, [music] it's 2:00 in the morning.
I'm at a motel.
It's 2:25 in the morning. I'm at a
motel. And I have to
I have to leave this motel in like 2
hours to try
to get on a ferry.
I'll explain,
but right now I got to go to bed.
Okay.
It's uh
Now it's 4:30. Got about 2 hours of
sleep.
Uh the sun is not out yet, but
I can hear birds chirping.
We got Time to go.
>> [music]
[music]
>> You got to be the first one to get
there. I'm not going to be the first one
to get there, but you got to be the
first one to get there. I shouldn't have
slept in. I shouldn't have slept in. I'm
going to be late. You really got to be
the first one to get there. This is
going to screw up my whole day. The
whole day. The whole summer.
Shoot, I'm late. I'm doing good. How you
doing?
>> to help you.
>> I'm
drive on standby.
>> Straight standby?
>> Yeah.
>> any reservation for today?
>> a res- Not for today.
>> Nothing for today? All right, hard
right.
>> Hard right.
Okay, this is what we're working with
here.
In order to get your car onto a boat,
you have to have a reservation.
I don't have a reservation cuz because
to have a reservation you have to plan
in advance. I
So, you show up early and they put you
on standby.
It could be an hour, it could be a week
and a half. You never know. But, that's
I'm trying to navigate that right now.
>> And don't lock it.
>> Thank you very much. We'll see you
later.
>> Have a good day.
>> So, I got this, but I
I still don't know what that means.
Either I'm going to get my car there
soon or eventually.
I'm hoping for soon.
>> Is this one yours?
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> You want me to move it up to the front?
>> No, I got to get the keys.
>> No, you're good right there.
>> If you want, I can put it right in the
front.
>> No,
I wish I could do that, but you can't.
>> You just let me know if anything
changes.
Just trying to sweet talk him.
>> [music]
>> So, sometimes you come here and there's
like two cars. You wait behind those two
cars and what happens is when other
people don't show up and there's room on
the boat, they then take the standby
car, my car, and they put it on the
boat. But, today there's not like two or
three cars, there's row after row after
row after row of cars waiting to get on
the boat.
Then at the end of all those rows,
there's another row and that row goes
all the way back and at the very end of
that row,
that's me. That's my car.
So, I leave the car and then I go and
get on this big, beautiful ship
on on foot. I walk on that big beautiful
ship. So, now I have to carry as much
stuff as possible.
First rule of Boy Scouts, be prepared.
I'm prepared for most any contingency.
This is my folding wagon. Positively
will not be able to get everything on
the folding
Ah.
Will not be able to get everything in
the folding wagon, but I will be able to
get a lot of
I will be able to get a lot of stuff.
One bag for Franny, one bag for Georgie,
one bag for me, one bag for Candace.
Okay.
That's it. Now I leave my car.
I'll see it again sometime. I don't know
when, but I'll see it again sometime.
>> [music]
>> Are you going on board?
>> I'm going on board.
>> Yeah, go ahead.
>> And that that is how you unsuccessfully
get your car don't get your car onto a
Steamship Authority ferry.
We're on it, though.
>> Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
Welcome aboard the Martha's Vineyard
ferry. I'd like to take a [music] moment
of your time to acquaint you with our
vessel.
>> [music]
>> 2 hours.
[music]
>> Land ho.
If you look closely on the horizon,
there's land there.
We're almost there.
We're getting close.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Piggy, where are we?
Where are the bunnies?
Well, I made it.
I guess this is the start of summer
vacation.
>> Yay!
Hooray!
>> Here [screaming] we go.
>> [music]